Top of the morning Siri, you ******. I'm
the candy man and I'm listening. More
video. I'm gonna screw you up. I'm gonna
Yeah, I'm gonna kill you. I'm gonna slice
you up. My parents will go for a
drunk delinquent. ********. I'm gonna
kill you. I'm gonna call you up. I'm
gonna kill you. I'm gonna eat your flesh.
I'm gonna eat your flesh and I'm gonna
eat your spaghetti. You are. You are a
prick 1. The ****
are you *******
******? ****** ******
****** ******. You
will eat my
****.
What you've eaten for face
for face, for French Facebook,
**** **** **** Facebook. I
will get you. I'm a
little you're a piddle and
a piddle I will ask
your prick you are a
worker and candyman to be
spread my candy to you
*******. Big **** face wonk
******** poof. You are a
poof poof. And I'm going
to eat you into the I send
this to everybody.
**** **** ****.
You are such an ***. You are such a
prick. You are a big fat ****
************. What about you?
You want the ******* PDF? Yes,
I am African, Yes, I am
Irish. I'm Irish and I want
to get a ******* killer.
**** world, even though we have an
award. What do you want? The news
for you? Who? Not for kids in
the ****. In the ****. Spring Dash.
Bing Dash.
When you fall. I
knew I was going to eat you
for grace. Come on. Kindly mine. Do
what? My candy.
You *********** into the
last piece of hell
you ever wear today,
for I am 21,
you see. Yes.
Lick my penis. I'm going over slice
you up. Boring. How dare you ****
you. **** you.
Come on, give me my booty
and I'll give you free. Let's
have a retreat. Muggy **** you
up. Come over here. I'll give
you some more. Give me the
click. I'll send you to Hall.
Eat my big ball. Another. Then
you'll see the. Flows from it
freely onto your face. For my fists. I'll
slash you up good, you little ****. I'm
an ******* but you are a ball. I'm
gonna come and it's forested and I'm
gonna throw in your face. You
************ ***** ***** ****. I am a
candyman that respects me. I am for
coming for thee. And I know that I
am the Riddle. The Riddle.
I tell you.
Yes, you hear me, don't you? I am a
reader. I am not like that Batman.
What is it with your focus? This is
my day. I wonder if you've already made
it in Ireland, baby.
And stop a trend you fight.
What are you?I find
you in the field, you ******* little
***** and I'll eat you alive. Or
a little delight. Sharpened delight, Yes.
What are your ************ and the
candyman? I'm coming for you and your
mother. Hope I come for you. And
I'll eat you too. And your mom
and your dog. Why?
Why are you conflict?
What is your name? Who are
you?
Now do some run whiskey from
or down the lane. It's a
pain, wolf. Go
away, I did
my crying. This
is my video
tape.
Yes, I did it.
My friend. What, what, what? Why?
Why? Why? Why? Why? Why? Why?
Why?
Yes, Yes, ma'am.
I say.
Yes, yes, yes. Why
are you pregnant with
my sister? ******* *******.
**** you.
Of to make my Stew, the Candyman.